Guide to the Sports Information Office: Photographic Negatives collection, circa 1924-1992, 1995, undated UA.13.02.0018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sports Information Office: Photographic Negatives collection
circa 1924-1992, 1995, undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. University Archives
Duke University. Sports Information Office
UA.13.02.0018
23 Linear Feet 20,122 items
Collection includes photographic negatives related to sports at Duke. Sports include the following: baseball, basketball, boxing, cheerleading, cross country, fencing, field hockey, football, golf, gymnastics, lacrosse, soccer, swimming, tennis, track, wrestling, and volleyball. There are also negatives that pertain to general athletics. The subjects of the negatives include athletes, coaches, team pictures, and game action. The collection ranges in date from 1924-1992, 1995, undated.
The collection includes nitrate, acetate, and likely polyester film bases. The nitrate is housed in an off-site nitrate storage facility. There is evidence to suggest that some of the nitrate is undergoing degradation. Some of the acetate is also undergoing acetate film base degradation. Most of the negatives tend to be approximately 4x5 inches, but sizes can vary. There are also color negatives within the collection.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
There are five (5) boxes of nitrate film (boxes 36, 37, 38, 39, and 40). These boxes are kept off-site in specialized housing and may not be recalled by patrons.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Arrangement
The Sports Information Office Photographic Negatives collection are arranged alphabetically by sport. There are between 1-5 subseries per sport: Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, Groups, Teams, Games, Miscellaneous.
The Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff subseries reflects the organization and identification imposed on the negatives by the photographer(s). Each person per sport is in alphabetical order. It was noted during processing that surnames were sometimes mis-spelled. Resources such as the school's yearbook (The Chanticleer) and the alumni directory were used to try and determine the correct spelling. There are also non-standard spellings of first and last names throughout the collection. Additionally, if a person was photographed with one other, those negatives appear in this subseries.
The Group subseries reflects negatives where more than two people are photographed together or groups of unidentified individuals. The identification for each group is listed in the order it was printed on the original acidic negative sleeve.
The Teams subseries provides images of individual teams from any given year. They may include full teams or partial teams, such as "relay team" or "long-distance team."
The Games subseries contains images of games, matches, practices, etc. Although it is noted that not every sport participates in "games," the term is used throughout for consistency sake.
Lastly, the Miscellaneous subseries generally includes negatives where the subject matter doesn't fit in any of the other series, and include images of facilities, trophies, football crowds, and band formations.
Historical note
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. For many years, the Sports Information Office has maintained records, photographs, and other material about Duke athletic teams.
Collection Overview
This collection contains 20,122 negatives related to sports at Duke, and they range in date from about 1924 to 1992, 1995 and undated. The sports represented are as follows: baseball, basketball, boxing, cheerleading, cross country, fencing, field hockey, football, golf, gymnastics, lacrosse, soccer, swimming, tennis, track, wrestling, and volleyball. There is a series for general athletics, which tends to include images of physical education instructors or coaches from all sports. There is also a series called "Undetermined," which lists individuals for whom no sport or tie to athletes could be determined.
The subjects within each series include athletes, coaches, athletic staff (such as secretaries and trainers), team pictures, game shots, trophies, and athletic fields and facilities. The athletes may have been photographed in uniform, in suits, or in letterman sweaters. They may have been photographed with family and/or friends. Oftentimes, the athletes were posed in faux action shots.
There are not very many images of women athletes, but there are some available, including a small number of images of Women's Athletic Association members playing baseball (not softball), basketball, and tennis.
Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University. University Archives; Duke University -- Sports; Duke University -- Sports -- History; Duke University--Students
- Baseball Negatives, circa 1926-1981; undated; 1
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 1
    - Abdella, David Dixon (Dixie), 1967-1969 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00001)
    - Adams, Bob, 1930, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04531)
    - Allen, Tom, 1930, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04532)
    - Allie, Butch, 1958 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00002)
    - Altman, Don, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00003)
    - Altman, Don and Coach Clarence "Ace" Parker, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00004)
    - Ambler, Merrill, 1962 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00005)
    - Ambler, Wayne, 1935, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04533)
    - Ambler, Wayne, 1936, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04534)
    - Ambler, Wayne, 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04535)
    - Arlen, Dan, 1969 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00006)
    - Atkinson, George, 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00007)
    - Ayers, Milton, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00008)
    - Baglien, Don, 1969 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00009)
    - Barker, Ralph "Buttercup," 1930, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04536)
    - Barley, George, 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04537)
    - Barrett, Drew James, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00010)
    - Barringer, Jerry, 1965 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00011)
    - Bass, Buddy, 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00012)
    - Bell, Sam, circa 1932, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04538)
    - Belue, Jean, circa 1928-1930, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04539)
    - Bennett, Tom, circa 1931, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04540)
    - Bensinger, Bob, 1951 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00013)
    - Bergeron, Bill, 1949 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00014)
    - Bergeron, Bill (alone and with Jerry Frye), 1949, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04541)
    - Bergman, Russ, 1938, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04542)
    - Bergman, Russ, 1938 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00015)
    - Bilane, Frank, 1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04543)
    - Bishop, Lon, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04544)
    - Blackburn, Tom, 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00016)
    - Blanchard, J. Randolph, Jr. (Randy), 1967-1969 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00017)
    - Blaney, Bernie, 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00018)
    - Bly, Jim (Coach), 1963 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00019)
    - Bochow, Bo, 1969 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00020)
    - Bonczek, Lonnie, 1956 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00021)
    - Bonczek, Lonnie, 1958 (with Coach Clarence "Ace" Parker) (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00022)
    - Bortz, Kilmer, 1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04545)
    - Bosson, Dave, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00023)
    - Bost, Bob, circa 1930-1933, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04546)
    - Bracy, Biff, 1963 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00024)
    - Bradsher, Arthur (copy negative of 1905 print), undated (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00025)
    - Braswell, Charlie, 1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04547)
    - Brewer, Dick, 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00026)
    - Browning, Art, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00027)
    - Brownstein, Mark, 1959 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00028)
    - Brunansky, Joe, 1938, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04548)
    - Burns, Tom, 1942, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04549)
    - Burton, Dick, 1956 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00029)
    - Buteau, Bernie, 1958 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00030)
    - Buschman, Craig Emmons, 1970 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00031)
    - Butters, Tom, 1968 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00032)
    - Butters, Tom, 1973, 1976, undated (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00033)
    - Byam, George, 1941, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04550)
    - Byam, George, 1941 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00034)
    - Byers, Bob, 1958 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00035)
    - Cappello, John, 1957 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00036)
    - Carey, Charles, 1939 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00037)
    - Carroll, John, 1951 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00038)
    - Carroll, Woody, 1942 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00039)
    - Carter, Samuel Henley (alone and with Carter Hill), 1967 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00040)
    - Carver, George "Lefty," 1953 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00041)
    - Casey, Tim, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00042)
    - Caskey, Claude, 1938, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04551)
    - Cavalier, Benny, 1951 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00043)
    - Challenger, Dave, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00044)
    - Challenger, John, 1957 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00045)
    - Cheek, Herb, 1934, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04552)
    - Chestnutt, Ed, 1963 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00046)
    - Chronister, Carl Stewart, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00047)
    - Clark, George, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00048)
    - Cline, Al, circa late 1960's (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00049)
    - Coble, Thomas Stanley III (Stan), 1965-1967, 1969 Apr. (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00050)
    - Cockrell, Andy, 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00051)
    - Cochrane, Archie [?], circa 1931-1933, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04553)
    - Colley, Nelson, circa 1931-1933, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04554)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, in coaching togs), circa 1929-1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04555)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, portraits), circa 1930s (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00052)
    - Combs, Jack (Coach), 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04556)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach), 1937, 1939 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00053)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with Chubby Dean), 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04557)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with Buck Herzog), circa 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04558)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, actively coaching players), 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04559)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, actively coaching players), 1937 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00054)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with players), 1937-1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04560)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with players), 1939 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00055)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with Coach Herschel Caldwell), 1939, circa 1945 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00056)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with Coach Herschel Caldwell), 1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04561)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with Coach Herschel Caldwell), 1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04562)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach,with Eric Tipton), 1939 Mar. 30 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00057)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with Herb Pennock - former Yankees pitcher), circa early 1940s, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04563)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with Nap Lajoie), circa late 1940s (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00058)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach), circa 1940-1943, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04564)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach), circa 1940-1943 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00059)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, with Bill McCahan, inside Duke Stores [?]), 1943, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04565)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, awards ceremony), 1952 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00060)
    - Coombs, Jack (Coach, Hall of Fame Award, pictured with Wallace Wade), 1954 Oct. (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00061)
    - Coombs, Raymond (Bobby), 1933, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04566)
    - Coombs, Raymond (Bobby) (with Coach Jack Coombs?), 1933 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00062)
    - Cornelius, Corky, 1935, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04567)
    - Corwin, Dick, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04568)
    - Crandell, John, 1938, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04569)
    - Crisson, Stan, 1963 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00063)
    - Crihfield, Steve, 1957 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00064)
    - Curtin, Walter, 1942 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00065)
    - Curtis, Al, 1949, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04570)
    - Curtis, Al, 1949 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00066)
    - D'Alonzo, Al, 1946, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00067)
    - D'Alonzo, Al, 1947, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04571)
    - Dailey, Dick, circa 1952-1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00068)
    - Daniel, John, 1961 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00069)
    - Daniels, Dorsey, 1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04572)
    - Davies, Mike, 1969 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00070)
    - Davis, Bob, 1951 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00071)
    - Davis, Brandon, 1947, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04573)
    - Davis, Brandon, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00072)
    - Davis, Lawrence Columbus "Crash," 1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04574)
    - Davis, Lawrence Columbus "Crash," 1940 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00073)
    - Davis, Larry Edward (Co-Captain, 1968), 1966-1968 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00074)
    - Davis, Ronnie, 1961 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00075)
    - Davis, Tom, 1942 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00076)
    - Davis, Tom, 1942-1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04575)
    - Dean, Chubby, 1936, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04576)
    - Dean, Chubby, 1936 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00077)
    - Dean, Dayton, circa 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04577)
    - Dean, Dayton, circa 1937; with Mrs. Coombs at baseball park, 1940 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00078)
    - Dean Brothers (Chubby and Dayton), 1938 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00079)
    - Denison, Steve, 1968 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00080)
    - Densmore, Dick, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00081)
    - DeRogatis, Al, 1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04578)
    - DeRogatis, Al, 1945 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00082)
    - Dodson, Nathan, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04579)
    - Domhoff, Bill, 1957 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00083)
    - Drye, Carl, 1958 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00084)
    - Duffy, Howard, circa 1930s, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04580)
    - Dunlevy, Charles, 1958 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00085)
    - Dutrow, George, 1956 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00086)
    - Ennis, Hugh, 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04581)
    - Erickson, Stu, 1947, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04582)
    - Erickson, Stu, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00087)
    - Ewing, Sam, 1934, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04583)
    - Fader, Bucky, 1962 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00088)
    - Fader, Bucky and Lynn Fader (Brooks), 1962 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00089)
    - Fader, Lynn (Brooks), 1962 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00090)
    - Faley, Dick, circa 1948-1951, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04584)
    - Falwell, John, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00091)
    - Farley, Roland (Boley), circa 1930, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04585)
    - Fatzinger, Harleigh, 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00092)
    - Felton, Carle, circa 1968-1970 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00093)
    - Felton, Eric, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04586)
    - Fesperman, W. D., 1954 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00094)
    - Flohr, Mortiz (Morty), 1934, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04587)
    - Folger, Fred, 1949 (includes action vs. Cornell), Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04588)
    - Freeze, Bill, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04589)
    - Frye, Jerry, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00095)
    - Frye, Jerry, 1949, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04590)
    - Frye, John, 1959 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00096)
    - Fye, Charlie, 1958 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00097)
    - Gaddy, Tom, 1939 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00098)
    - Gantt, Bob (copy negative of 1908 image), undated (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00099)
    - Garcia, Bill, 1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04591)
    - Gibbons, John, 1951 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00100)
    - Glacken, Scotty, 1965 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00101)
    - Godd, Dick, circa late 1930s, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04592)
    - Goodman, Billy, 1954 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00102)
    - Graham, Frank, 1949, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04593)
    - Graham, Frank, 1949 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00103)
    - Gregory, Dick, 1962 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00104)
    - Griffeth, Leon (Lee), 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04594)
    - Griffeth, Leon (Lee), 1946, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04595)
    - Groat, Dick, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00105)
    - Groat, Dick, 1952 (receiving an award in baseball) (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00106)
    - Groat, Dick, undated (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00107)
    - Groat, Dick, 1952 (in Cardinals and Pirates uniforms) (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00108)
    - Groome, Carlyle, 1942, 1946 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00109)
    - Grove, Bob, 1940, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04596)
    - Gutekunst, John, 1966 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00110)
    - Halliday, Bill, 1946, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04597)
    - Hancock, Jack, 1949, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04598)
    - Hanenberg, William J. (Bill), 1970 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00111)
    - Harkrader, Lacy (Lakey), circa 1931-1934, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04599)
    - Harner, Harry, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04600)
    - Harrington, Milton, circa 1928-1931, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04601)
    - Harrison, Larry, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00112)
    - Hartman, Marly, 1978 Feb. (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00113)
    - Hawkins, Lee, circa 1927-1930, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04602)
    - Hawn, Bobby, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00114)
    - Hayes, Bill, 1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04603)
    - Hendrickson, Horace, 1934, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04604)
    - Hessler, Bob, 1942, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04605)
    - Hewlett, Marvin, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04606)
    - Hill, Rufus Carter III (Carter), 1965-1967 (co-captain, 1967) (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00115)
    - Hines, John Moore (John), 1965-1967 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00116)
    - Hochreiter, Pete, 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00117)
    - Holloway, David Michael (Mike), 1966-1968 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00118)
    - Holloway, Steve, 1963 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00119)
    - Holtzman, Thomas W. "Tink," 1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04607)
    - Hoover, George, 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00120)
    - Hopkins, Jim, 1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04608)
    - Hoppe, Dick, 1952 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00121)
    - Houghton, Bob, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04609)
    - Houghton, Bob, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00122)
    - Howell, Ed, circa 1930-1932, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04610)
    - Hoye, Frank, 1938, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04611)
    - Hoye, Frank, 1938 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00123)
    - Huiskamp, William (Bill), 1935, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04612)
    - Huiskamp, Carl, 1934, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04613)
    - Hysong, Jim, circa 1967 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00124)
    - Ingham, Bill, 1942, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04614)
    - Jackson, Gordon S., Jr. (Gordy), 1969 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00125)
    - Jenkins, John, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00126)
    - Jessup, Bill, 1940, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04615)
    - Johnson, David L. (Dave), 1968 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00127)
    - Johnson, Dick, 1951 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00128)
    - Jurgensen, Christian "Sonny," 1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00129)
    - Kale, Wallace (with Samuel Rothbaum), 1941, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04616)
    - Kalish, Ron, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00130)
    - Karukstis, Paul, circa 1947-1949, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04617)
    - Kast, Fred, 1959 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00131)
    - Keller, Herky, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00132)
    - Kerr, Red, 1938, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04618)
    - Kersey, Art, 1938, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04619)
    - Kiefer, John, 1969 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00133)
    - Kiely, Tom, 1947, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04620)
    - Kiely, Tom, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00134)
    - Kirkpatrick, Dave, 1954 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00135)
    - Kistler, Henry, 1928, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04621)
    - Klare, Bob, circa 1931-1933, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04622)
    - Klein, John, 1959 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00136)
    - Klein, Lewis, 1949 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00137)
    - Kohler, Ervin, 1942 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00138)
    - Konopka, Al, 1935, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04623)
    - Kreutzer, Dick, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00139)
    - Lapp, Bob, 1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04624)
    - Lattimore, Bert, 1958 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00140)
    - Lauro, John, 1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04625)
    - Lea, Bill, 1951 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00141)
    - Leclercq, Bob, 1953 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00142)
    - Leopoldt, Richard W. (Kick), 1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04626)
    - Lewis, Joe, 1953 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00143)
    - Liana, Frank, 1935, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04627)
    - Liana, Frank, 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04628)
    - Liccardo, Jim, 1966 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00144)
    - Lieber, Todd M., 1966 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00145)
    - Lindsay, Carl, circa 1948-1950, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04629)
    - Lippincott, Victor, 1959 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00146)
    - Little, Ed, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04630)
    - Little, Frank, 1945, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04631)
    - Lucas, Charlie (Red), 1947, 1949 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00147)
    - Lucas, Charlie (Red), 1949, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04632)
    - Mack, Connie, Jr., 1934, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04633)
    - Marley, Roy, 1962 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00148)
    - Marshall, Archie, 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04634)
    - Matherly, Eugene, 1944, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04635)
    - Matheson, Cy, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00149)
    - May, Reynolds, 1935, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04636)
    - Maynard, Pete, 1957 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00150)
    - Maynard, Pete (with Deems Allie), 1959 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00151)
    - McAfee, George, 1940, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04637)
    - McCahan, Bill, 1941, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04638)
    - McCahan, Bill, 1941, 1942 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00152)
    - McCarthy, Ed, 1947, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04639)
    - McCarthy, Ed, 1947 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00153)
    - McCracken, Dean, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Item UA13020018-N-00154)
    - McGrey, Jim, 1939, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04640)